I take it back. I take it back.
No, my mom had me when she was 16, and I'm very against abortion.
I take it back.
I respect that.
I'm speaking generally about stupid.
But it's also not relevant to the conversation.
No, that's the thing, because most people who defend animal rights,
most people who are going around defending animal rights,
go and say that you have an abortion and kill a human being.
And most people who want to go around defending murder animals
find other excuses for reasons why they can do it.
Like, oh, do you believe in abortion?
So you're running around...
So you're doing the same thing, you're stupid.
Wait, but we're eating, the chicken's going to get eaten.
It's unnecessary.
It's unnecessary, and it's not...
I know, but that's...
Hashem gave us everything we need with the plants.
But that's humanity.
Humanity eats meat.
Always has.
But that wasn't Hashem's design.
Genesis 1-29.
Yeah, but then the flood happened.
Yeah, that was because of the fall.
That was because of Hamas and Shekath.
Violence filled the earth.
This violence filled the earth.
I'm going to do my research.
And the earth was cleansed of it.
By the word of Hashem, it will be cleansed again if we don't stop.
At the time when they were vegans is when the violence came.
No, it wasn't because of the righteous.
Wait, no, wait, wait, just get the order right.
I don't know, it might...
During the vegan era, it's when the Hamas...
You gotta watch, yeah.
Then there was the flood.
It came to the flesh again.
Wait, that is...
But Kirk, do you agree that that is the...
I'll give you an update.
The Hamas era, I promise.
The vegans brought us a flood.
No.
Yes.
No, wait.
No, the righteous line was...
The vegan, the time...
No, the righteous line did not.
That's why they were spared.
And why Noah went on the ark.
Why was there a...
Who did the Hamas?
Everyone was vegans.
No, the...
According to the scripture,
there were the fallen ones and the Nephilim
taught humanity to do violence to animals
and consume them
and drink their blood
and shed their blood.
I don't know which Bible you read.
That's from Enoch.
Hello, hello, hello, hello.
No, no, you were talking to people.
You changed the subject now.
It doesn't apply Enoch to here.
God tells Noah...
God tells Noah after the flood,
eat the...
You can eat the animals.
The Remus.
Eat the animals.
He says you can eat animals, right?
No, Remus.
Animals...
Remus or bugs?
Yeah, that's bugs.
It's a concession for a survival situation.
No, call the...
You read the Masoretic, yeah?
The Masoretic?
The Masoretic text.
Of the Tanakh, the Hebrew.
The block letters.
He's good, he's good.
He's good, but he's a little fuzzy,
what you're saying.
Wait a sec.
The vegan era brought the flood.
You're bringing in Remus and Enoch,
and Book of Enoch,
which you know I don't believe in
and I've never read.
But what I'm saying is...
And it's not considered a Jewish class called that.
Well, you do keporos,
which is not in the Tanakh or the Torah.
This is true.
It's made up.
How many...
So, made up?
Yeah, it's just made up,
laid out of garbage
to justify slaughtering beings for no reason.
So...
That's revolt.
Huh?
Yeah.
See, that's why the cages are red.
Do the...
Do the change.
That's compassionate.
That's merciful.
I hear you.
I respect religious tradition
when it doesn't harm others.
Wait a sec.
There's no need to harm these...
So, where does the money go to
when you do it with money?
What are you supposed to do with the money?
I'm pretty sure it goes to the poor, right?
Yeah.
So, what do you think happens to the chickens?
Some of them go to the poor.
Most of them go to the trash.
The goal, the intent is that they go to the poor.
Yeah, well, they don't.
And...
They do a lot of them.
And the whole sin transfer,
feeding the poor,
the sins of everyone.
I mean, it's just...
And these...
Okay.
So, you say.
But it's important.
So, these beings
are meant to live.
They have the Ruach.
They have the Nefesh.
But maybe this is the whole reason
they're here for.
I mean, you can't argue against that.
I mean, it's not a convincing argument.
There is no maybe.
Hashem was very clear
in Genesis chapter 1
that all animals were cursed.
A lot of people
would be sick of this for this.
What do we do?
Which is, the root is Yerat,
which is to lower oneself in service
to, we're meant to serve...
That's why I'm here, baby.
It's not dominating them.
It's going to kill them and murder them.
That's what we're here to do.
But this is utilizing...
Wait, wait, what is the point
of us doing this?
The point is that we be better.
We realize, really,
this was our faith.
The point of the chicken
is for the person to realize
that the death
which is coming on the chicken,
you have a tender moment
with the chicken
and he's going to die.
He's going to get murdered.
And right, so do you think
I feel happy towards the chicken?
The tender moment
towards the murder
is the same feeling
that Jeffrey Dahmer
felt about his egg.
Wrong, wrong meat, man.
But he might eat them
and eat them first.
But the whole tender moment
and all that
makes it that much more psychotic.
All the tender stuff
We're meant to love animals.
The superiority of the human race
is in production.
Meaning, these guys...
- No worries.
- No, what did you say?